Jumbo Jottings UP157
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Jumbo Jottings
1981 -- 1995
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Tufts Jumbo Club Inc.
UP157
0.25 Linear Feet
Arrangement
This collection is organized into one series.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains issues of Jumbo Jottings, a publication of Tufts Jumbo Club. It contains information relating to college sports and caters mainly to alumni.
Biographical / Historical
Tufts Jumbo Club was an alumni organization founded in 1969 to provide financial support for Tufts athletic facilities and teams, and to provide recognition to members of Tufts' athletic community. At its peak, the Jumbo Club had over 1,000 dues-paying members, making it one of the largest alumni groups at Tufts. The Club was responsible for planning the annual Jumbo Club Awards banquet, a tradition that began in the spring of 1970. In addition to honoring Tufts athletes and coaches, the Jumbo Club also presented an annual Distinguished Achievement Award in coordination with Tufts Athletics Department, which recognized local athletic figures of note. Recipients included Nancy Kerrigan, Robert Kraft, and Joan Benoit Samuelson. Tufts Jumbo Club recorded notable happenings in their newsletter, Jumbo Jottings.
- Jumbo jottings, 1981 -- 1995; UP157.001; 0.25 Linear Feet
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains issues of Jumbo Jottings, a publication of Tufts Jumbo Club. It contains information relating to college sports and caters mainly to alumni.
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged chronologically
  Conditions Governing Access
  Open for research.
  - Jumbo Jottings, 1981-09; UP157.001.001.00001 (Box 1)
  - Jumbo Jottings, 1982-01; UP157.001.001.00002 (Box 1)
  - Jumbo Jottings Fall, 1982; UP157.001.001.00003 (Box 1)
  - Jumbo Jottings Winter, 1982 -- 1983; UP157.001.001.00004 (Box 1)
  - Jumbo Jottings Fall, 1983; UP157.001.001.00005 (Box 1)
  - Jumbo Jottings Fall, 1984; UP157.001.001.00006 (Box 1)
  - Jumbo Jottings Winter, 1984; UP157.001.001.00007 (Box 1)
  - Jumbo Jottings Summer, 1985; UP157.001.001.00008 (Box 1)
  - Jumbo Jottings Winter, 1985; UP157.001.001.00009 (Box 1)
  - Jumbo Jottings Summer, 1985; UP157.001.001.00010 (Box 1)
  - Jumbo Jottings Winter, 1985 -- 1986; UP157.001.001.00011 (Box 1)
  - Jumbo Jottings Summer, 1986; UP157.001.001.00012 (Box 1)
  - Jumbo Jottings Summer, 1987; UP157.001.001.00015 (Box 1)
  - Jumbo Jottings Fall, 1988; UP157.001.001.00016 (Box 1)
  - Jumbo Jottings Winter, 1988; UP157.001.001.00017 (Box 1)
  - Jumbo Jottings Spring, 1988; UP157.001.001.00018 (Box 1)
  - Jumbo Jottings Summer, 1989; UP157.001.001.00019 (Box 1)
  - Jumbo Jottings Summer, 1990; UP157.001.001.00020 (Box 1)
  - Jumbo Jottings Summer, 1991; UP157.001.001.00021 (Box 1)
  - Jumbo Jottings Winter, 1991; UP157.001.001.00022 (Box 1)
  - Jumbo Jottings Winter, 1992 -- 1993; UP157.001.001.00023 (Box 1)
  - Jumbo Jottings Spring, 1994; UP157.001.001.00024 (Box 1)
  - Jumbo Jottings Summer, 1995; UP157.001.001.00025 (Box 1)